correct
對了
The cargo ship has been arranged
貨船已經安排好了
I'll be on the high seas at noon tomorrow
明天中午啊 會在公海
The area you are familiar with is waiting for you.
你熟悉的區域等你
By the time
到時候
You use this yacht to go out to sea
你就用這艘遊艇出海
knew
知道了
have you ever thought about it
你有想過
Life after leaving?
離開以後的生活嗎
Have thought about it
想過啊
Go to Australia
去澳洲
Buy a small house by the beach
海邊買個小房子
settle down
安定下來
I go out to sea every day
每天就是出出海
fishing
捕捕魚
Change your life
換一種活法
Will you find me?
你呢 會去找我嗎
fine
挺好的
You know me
你知道我
What do you like about you?
喜歡你哪點嗎
Can cook
會做飯
what else
還有什麼
I think
我覺得啊
There is something about you
你身上有一種
let people bathe in
讓人沐浴在
feeling under the sun
陽光下的感覺
Very passionate about life
對生活還特別熱忱
it may be because
可能是因為
I don’t have it myself, right?
我自己身上沒有吧
I hope
我希望
You have to keep these forever
你要永葆這些
you can also have
你也可以有
if you are willing to give up
如果你願意放棄的話
life
人生嘛
It's a trade-off
本來就是在取捨
trade-off
取捨
everyone will say
每個人都會說
How many can do this?
能做到的有幾個呢
I can do it
我就可以啊
How many people are like you?
哪有幾個人像你一樣啊
But you don’t know either
可是你也不知道
what you have now
你現在擁有的東西
How long can I have it?
到底能擁有多久啊
yes
是啊
so
所以
I try my best to make everything happen
我盡力讓所有的事情
time to have
能夠擁有的時間
longer
更長一點
Even if it costs more
哪怕付出更多的代價
I hope I can afford it
但願付得起吧
today
今天
could be us
可能是我們
The last time we met
最後一次見面了
This doesn't sound like anything
這聽起來不像是什麼
Something to celebrate
值得慶祝的事
Separation is also the beginning
分別也是開始
Decided
決定了
I don't need your boat
我不用你的船
Why
為什麼
fishing club boat
海釣俱樂部的船
They all stop at this pier
都停在這個碼頭
Getting one is for me
搞一艘對我來說
It's not that difficult, right?
沒那麼難吧
All are leaving
都要走了
Don't bother you anymore
就別連累你了
separate wine
分別的酒
Now that it has fallen
既然已經倒上了
That is
那就是
It's time for me to leave
我要離開的時候了
Stop drinking
別喝了
Live the life you want
去過你想要的生活吧
Chen Ting
陳婷
This bottle of wine belongs to Boss Zhang
這瓶酒是張老闆
Give it to me
送我的吧
She thinks you disappeared
她覺得你消失了
I will be safe
我才會安全
for no more
對於不再有
people who take advantage of value
利用價值的人
can be discarded at any time
隨時可以丟棄
This is her style
這就是她的作風
Do you want to continue to work for them?
還要繼續為他們賣命嗎
let's go together
我們一起走
get out of here
離開這兒
sorry
對不起
I can't leave
我走不了
Tomorrow afternoon
明天中午
The ship will still be waiting for you on the high seas
船還會在公海等著你
We'll never see each other again
我們再也見不到了吧
Live the life you want
去過自己想要的生活
It's a lucky thing
是件幸運的事情
What if I have an accident
萬一我出了意外
You will not
你不會的
I mean just in case
我是說萬一
What if I never see you again?
萬一我再也見不著你了
I hope you have what you want
我希望你所想所願
All can be achieved
都能實現
Have a safe journey
一路平安
Go quickly
快走
You get off the boat and hide over there
你下船那邊躲躲
That yacht
那艘遊艇啊
There has been no record of going overseas recently
最近一直沒有出海記錄
Is anyone living there now?
現在裡邊有人住嗎
Didn't pay much attention to this
這個沒太注意
After all, yachts come in and out more often
畢竟遊艇出入得比較多
Which ship?
哪艘啊
This is the one
就這艘啊
Why did you leave today without reporting?
怎麼沒報備今天就走了
Is it this ship?
是這艘嗎
yes
是
Immediately notify the Coast Guard for support
馬上通知海警支援
intercept that boat
截住那艘艇
clear
明白
Don't be nervous. Don't be nervous.
別緊張 別緊張
I'm just handling the fish
我只是在處理魚
Not finished yet
還沒處理完
can you wait for me for a while
可以等我一會兒嗎
Continue
繼續了啊
Stop running
不跑了
I can't even run.
跑也跑不了啊
Why are you still going to all the trouble?
幹嘛還費勁巴力地
Struggle
掙扎呀
like this fish
就像這魚
I also struggled after I got hooked.
上鈎之後也掙扎過
In the end, I just did it to myself
最後不過是搞得自己
Just bruised all over
遍體鱗傷而已
I still need some time
我還要點時間啊
If you don't mind
你們不介意的話
You can sit and wait
可以坐著等
There are baked cookies over there
那邊有烤好的餅乾
random
隨意
You've been hiding on this yacht
你一直躲在這個遊艇上
Not hiding
不是躲
is to live
是住
I love living on a yacht
我喜歡住在遊艇上
Available all year round
一年四季都可以
every morning and evening
每天早上和傍晚
It’s the best time for sea fishing
是海釣最好的時候
Especially this sea area
尤其這片海域
It's fishing season now
現在正值漁季
marvelous
太棒了
is good
是不錯
But you fish for yourself
但是你自己釣魚
It must be too lonely
未免也太孤單了吧
Who is the person who will help you?
接應你的人誰啊
Is there anyone who can help me?
哪有什麼人接應啊
I am an outcast
我是一個被拋棄的人
That is, relying on previous relationships
也就是靠著之前的關係
Borrowed this yacht
借了這艘遊艇
Now you're causing trouble
現在給人惹了麻煩
I still feel a little sorry.
還有點過意不去呢
Are you working with Yunyi Group now?
你現在是在跟雲逸集團
Clear the relationship?
撇清關係嗎
they are just my clients
他們只是我的客戶
I can tell you my upline
我可以告訴你我的上線
Who?
誰啊
Boss Zhang
張老闆
Who is Boss Zhang?
張老闆是誰啊
Don't you want to try it?
你不想嚐嚐嗎
if you are willing to
如果你願意
Say a few more words
多說兩句的話
I'm still in the mood to taste it
我還是有心情品嘗的
missed this time
錯過了這次
I won't have the chance to do it again in the future
以後可就沒機會再做了
Han Jie
韓傑
me to you
我對你
I still know a lot about it
多少還是有瞭解的
You are a person who loves life
你是一個熱愛生活的人
why do you want to be a spy
你為什麼要做間諜
adventurous
喜歡冒險
like challenges
喜歡挑戰
like
喜歡
exciting things
刺激的事
Are you satisfied with this answer?
這個答案你滿意嗎
have you ever thought about
你有沒有想過
The stimulation you want
你要的這份刺激
has harmed the interests of the country
已經危害到國家的利益
I know
我知道
Don’t you deserve it now?
現在不是罪有應得了嗎
Don’t you really want to try it?
你真的不嚐嚐嗎
Taste quite good
口感相當不錯
Pufferfish is a dangerous food
河豚是個危險的食物
In the final analysis, I just don’t dare to taste it.
那說到底就是不敢嘗啊
That's right
沒錯
Everyone knows that pufferfish is poisonous
都知道河豚有毒
But there are still so many people
但還是有那麼多人
like to eat it
喜歡吃它
The so-called poisonous and fresh
所謂至毒至鮮
I'm afraid that's it
恐怕就是如此吧
like us
就像我們這樣的
I knew something was wrong
明知道出一點岔子
What will happen?
會是什麼樣的下場
but
但是
Still can't escape
還是無法脫離
To put it bluntly, that’s
說白了就是
your benefits
你的所獲利益
Enough to make you willing to take risks
足夠讓你甘願受險
What a pity for such a good fish
可惜這麼好的魚了
Those poisonous ones are all there.
那有毒的都在那兒呢
I know
我知道
Now is not the time to taste
現在不是品嘗的時候
You and I can be regarded as equals in chess
你我也算是棋逢對手
Let's have a drink
咱倆喝一杯
maybe i can tell you more
也許我能告訴你更多
Han Jie
韩杰
i have given it to you
我已經給你
enough time
足夠的時間了
Who is Boss Zhang?
張老闆是誰
I don’t know who Boss Zhang is either.
我也不知道張老闆是誰
but
但是
This bottle of wine was given to me by her
這瓶酒是她送我的
Han Jie
韩杰
boss
老闆
There is a police officer outside looking for you
外面有警官找你
knew
知道了
Han Jie has been hiding
韓傑一直躲在
on your yacht
你的遊艇上
do you know
你知道嗎
I know
我知道
Not only I know
不光我知道
my secretary
我的祕書
Even the account manager knows it too
還有客戶經理也都知道
He often borrowed our boat
他經常借我們的船
Go fishing
出去海釣
He is our supplier
他是我們的供貨商
So we have kept
所以我們一直保持著
Good working relations
良好的合作關係
What's wrong with him?
他是出了什麼問題嗎
What happened to Han Jie?
韓傑怎麼了
His body was seen
有人看見他的屍體
Transported away by national security
被國安運走了
You shouldn't be sad now
你現在不應該傷心
should be thankful
應該慶幸
Glad he didn't fall
慶幸他沒有落到
In the hands of Guoan
國安手裡
I can't be as cold-blooded as you
我做不到像你這麼冷血
Only by being cold-blooded can you protect yourself
冷血才能保住你自己
Don't forget your identity
別忘了你的身份
I hope you will
我希望你以後
Don't make this mistake again
不要再犯這樣的錯誤
otherwise
否則
Everything you have worked so hard for
你辛辛苦苦得來的一切
you
你
and the person behind you
和你背後的人
They will all be like Han Jie
都會像韓傑
Same fate
一樣的下場
Hello
喂
Sister, I'm here
姐 我到了
when are you coming over
你什麼時候過來
I am coming over now
我馬上過來
goodbye
再見
How about it
怎麼樣
Is this location okay?
這位置可以吧
I was
我當時啊
I fell in love with it at first glance
一眼就看上了
The rent was paid on the same day
當天就把租金給付了
Find peace amidst the noise
鬧中取靜
This exhibition hall was really well chosen.
這展館選得確實不錯
Especially this trademark
尤其是這個商標
Very chic
很別緻
I'll take a photo
我拍一個
Then let's go in and take a look
那咱們進去看看
Good to go
好 走
Fang Lu
方陸
Sister Ting
婷姐
Secretary Zheng
鄭祕書
It's rare to have free time
難得有空啊
Xiao Lu’s business is my business
小陸的事就是我的事
Then let's go in and take a look together
那咱們一起進去看看
good
好
Walk
走
please
請
Come
來
This way
這邊
Look at the shape of this gate
您看這個大門的形狀
This material
這個材質
Matte Black
磨砂黑
Help me check the Cloud Art Museum
幫我查一下雲美術館
These just arrived
這些都是剛到的
I haven’t had time to show it yet.
還沒來得及擺呢
The exhibition hall is above
展廳在上面
Let's go up and have a look
咱們上去看看
Walk
走
All the decorations here
這兒所有的裝修
It’s all Fang Lu alone
都是方陸一個人
Completed by supervisor
監工完成的
Mayor Fang saw it
方市長看到了
It will definitely be gratifying
一定會很欣慰的
This matter has nothing to do with him
這事跟他沒什麼關係
He wouldn't care either
他也不會關心吧
Slower
慢點
Are you okay?
沒事吧
This is in Exhibition Hall 3
這個在三號展廳
Turn right ahead
前面右轉
Slower
慢点
National Security Bureau
國安局
Looking for resort hotels
正在查度假酒店的
Signal tower
信號塔
Why is the national security involved?
怎麼牽扯到國安了呀
There's some trouble
出了點麻煩
I see
我知道了
I'll take care of it
我會處理的
I'm tired
有勞了
Is there any problem with Xiao Lu?
小陸這邊還有什麼問題
tell me quickly
趕快跟我說
I'm next to him
有我在他旁邊
do not worry
你放心
I still have a job
我還有工作
I go first
我先走了
round trip
往返
Hi-tech
高科
Come in
進來
Qin Chu, look for me
秦處 你找我
This inspection report is out
這個檢驗報告出來了
There's poison in this sake
這個清酒裡面有毒液
This Han Jie
這個韓傑呀
Desire to die
一心求死
Didn't give any clues
也沒說出什麼線索來
Why does he want to die?
他為什麼一心求死
perhaps
或許
Protect others
保護其他人吧
Who?
谁啊
Chen Ting
陈婷
Then you find that between them
那你發現他們之間
Is there any close connection?
有什麼緊密的聯繫了嗎
There is no evidence yet
暫時沒有任何的證據
But Han Jie and Chen Ting
但是韓傑和陳婷
There are many intersections
有很多的交集
She knows Han Jie
她知道韓傑
When I was a spy
是間諜的時候
too calm
過於冷靜
It feels like I was prepared
感覺早有準備似的
so what
所以呢
I paid attention to her movements
我就留意了她的動向
I found out that she went to Yun Art Museum
我發現她去了雲美術館
Cloud Art Museum
雲美術館
Where is the legal person?
法人呢
It's Fang Lu
是方陸
Chen Ting also participated in the stock market
陳婷也參了股了
Fang Lu
方陆
Why do I hear this name?
我怎麼聽這個名字
So familiar
這麼耳熟啊
Fang Yongping's son
方永平的兒子
Fang Yongping
方永平
I know him
我認識他啊
He was the district mayor for the past two years
這前兩年他是區長
He is now the deputy mayor
他現在已經是副市長了
Yes, that's him
對 就是他
That means you doubt Chen Ting
那就是說你懷疑陳婷
It's the boss Zhang behind him
是背後那個張老闆
If she were Boss Zhang
如果她是張老闆的話
It would be too easy to kill Han Jie
那殺死韓傑那太容易了
right
對
As for Boss Zhang, she can’t be
就張老闆她不可能是
Such a loving person
那麼一個兒女情長的人
But this Chen Ting’s background
但這個陳婷的背景
It must not be simple
一定不簡單
Okay, go and do your work
行了 你去忙吧
If you need anything, call me again
你有什麼事再叫我
good
好
Where is sister?
姐 這兒呢
here here here
這兒 這兒 這兒
Let's go
走吧
What's wrong with the hand?
手怎麼了
How about going out to play?
怎麼出去玩一趟
Came back like this
弄成這樣回來了
Where is the boyfriend?
男朋友呢
Stop asking
你別問了
Very dizzy
頭暈得很
Okay, okay, don’t ask, don’t ask
好好好 不問不問
What do you want to eat?
想吃啥呀
I'll make you some soup when I get back.
回去給你煲個湯
Make some porridge
煮個粥
I want to drink
我想喝酒
Isn't this hurtful?
這不是傷了身哪
Are you sad?
你是傷了心吧
Don't talk nonsense. Are you going or not?
別廢話 你去不去
Stay with me to the end
奉陪到底呀
I don't just want to drink
我不光想喝酒
I still want to hit someone
我還想打人呢
You are like this now
你現在這樣
Who can you beat?
你能打過誰呀
Look at your face
看你這一臉
Lifeless look
了無生趣的樣子
or
要不
Find an interesting place
找個有意思的地方
Take you to have fun
帶你樂呵樂呵去
Okay
行啊
Walk
走
Slow down
你慢點啊
What kind of injury is this?
這受了什麼傷啊
It couldn't have been the man who hit it, right?
不會是那男的打的吧
tell me the truth
你跟我說實話
If it's really that man
要真是那個男的
Didn’t you say that you didn’t say it?
不是說了不說了嗎
Where is your car parked?
你那車呢 停哪兒了
over there
那兒呢
boarding
上車
Hello everyone
大家好
Welcome to the talk show scene
歡迎來到脫口秀的現場
Just mentioned
剛剛有說到
I am a Jiangxi person
我是一個江西人
Everyone is on the streets of Jinhai
大家有在津海的街頭
Have you ever eaten Jiangxi food?
吃過江西菜嗎
No
沒有
Give me a glass of Classic wine
給我來一杯古典酒
Give her a glass of orange juice
給她來杯橙汁吧
Wait a minute
等會兒
give me a drink
給我來一杯
Stronger wine, thank you
烈點的酒 謝謝
Then come and have a cup of bittersweetness
那來杯苦盡甘來吧
Can
可以
How can you still drink like this?
你這樣還能喝酒啊
Alcohol sterilizes
酒精殺菌嘛
Can also tell cold jokes
還能講冷笑話
Explain that it's no big deal
說明啊 沒什麼大事
It wasn't a big deal to begin with.
本來也就沒什麼大事啊
But that's it
不過就是
Lost in love
失個戀嘛
A romantic getaway turns into a breakup trip
浪漫之旅變成分手之旅
You chose the place unluckily.
你是地方選得不吉利啊
It’s not that the place is unlucky
不是地方不吉利
I chose the wrong career
是我選錯了職業
What does this have to do with career?
這跟職業有什麼關係啊
what does he do
他是幹什麼的
peers
同行
Hello, thank you for your hard work.
您好 您的苦盡甘來
Thanks
謝謝
hello your classic wine
您好 您的古典酒
I said
我說
Brother, I will do it next time
大哥 我下次我就
Bring a book with geography maps
帶一本書地理圖來
I said, brother, look
我說 大哥 你看
This is Jiangxi
這裡是江西
This is Xiangxi
這裡是湘西
Xiangni means Hunan
湘呢 是湖南的意思
The elder brother said that Hunan is Hunan
大哥說湘是湖南
Is that west Jiangxi?
那西是不是江西啊
trouble
麻煩
One more drink, thank you
再來一杯 謝謝
two cups
兩杯
Colleagues are enemies
同行是冤家
But that's not the case
但是也不至於
Because we break up now
因為這就分手啊
Which company is he from?
他是哪個公司的
How about digging it for him?
要不給他挖到
Our company is coming
咱們公司來
Too late
來不及啦
This man is too cautious
這男的太小心眼了
I lied to him
是我騙了他
I said I lied to him
我說是我騙了他
I started from the beginning
我從一開始
Just didn't tell him
就沒有告訴他
what do i do
我是幹什麼的
Where is this going?
這都哪兒跟哪兒啊
What are we doing?
咱們幹的不是什麼
A shady job
見不得光的工作啊
You do not understand
你不懂
Have a drink
喝酒吧
elder sister
姐姐
Is this going to be bigger?
這是要往大了整是嗎
If so, please let me know in advance.
是的話你提前吱個聲
I'll bring a strong man to prepare
我搖個壯漢來備著
Carry it back for you
給你背回去
I'm so weak and boneless
我這麼柔弱無骨的
I can't carry you
我可扛不動你啊
Do not worry
你放心吧
I don't drink much
我喝不大
Please have another drink. Thank you.
麻煩再來一杯 謝謝
Next we have a talk show
接下來我們脫口秀
There is a topic called
有一個主題叫做
lies in love
愛情中的謊言
Of course
當然啊
Some statistics say
有統計說
On average, boys every day
男生平均每天
Will lie six times
會撒六次謊
Girls only pee three times
女生只撒三次
Look at the young lady smiling
看小姐姐笑了
Have you lied recently?
最近是不是撒謊了
There are also statistics saying that
也有統計說啊
Saying that lies actually lead to
說其實謊言是導致
The culprit of breakups
分手的罪魁禍首
certainly
當然
What if you didn't lie?
如果你不撒謊呢
Then you can divide it faster
那你分得更快
Is there any audience in the audience?
台下有沒有觀眾
Can you come on stage and share it?
可以上台來分享一下
My own funny story
自己好笑的故事
Do you have
有沒有
Those who come on stage can be rewarded
上台的可以獎勵
A glass of tequila
龍舌蘭一杯
Up up up up
上 上上上
let's go
上吧
Of course you can also do it on site
當然你也可以現場
Drink it and bring it back
把它喝了再上來啊
Encourage everyone to be brave enough to take the stage
鼓勵大家勇敢上台
glass of tequila
一杯龍舌蘭
that
那個
I want to try
我想試試
We welcome with applause
我們掌聲歡迎
This brave girl
這位勇敢的姑娘
What are you doing?
幹嘛呀
Let me try
我試試
Don't be impulsive
別衝動啊
If you want to beat him
你要是想揍他
Go back and wait until he gets off work
回頭等他下班了
I'll get you a set of sacks
我給你弄一麻袋一套
It's not too late for you to beat him again
你再揍他也不遲啊
You
你呀
Don't worry
你就放心吧
I can't kill him
我打不死他
Give this guy another round of applause
再次以掌聲送給這位
Brave and beautiful young lady
勇敢美麗的小姐姐
OK OK
好 好 好
I show my hand
我攤牌了
Actually I'm a spy
其實我是一名間諜
my boyfriend
我男朋友
What's the reason for breaking up with me?
跟我分手的原因呢
Just because my identity was exposed
就是因為我身份暴露了
I believe it
我相信啊
There will definitely be someone at this time
這個時候一定會有人
Want to ask
想問了
What's wrong with being a spy?
這當間諜怎麼了呢
This is spying
這當間諜
Does it affect falling in love?
就影響談戀愛了嗎
it is nothing more than a
它無非就是一個
It's a dangerous profession
很危險的職業嘛
right
對不對
Actually I thought so too
其實我也是這麼想的
What did he say?
那他怎麼說呢
he said very angrily
他非常氣憤地說
He said I don't care
他說我不在乎
are you a spy
你是不是一個間諜
but you can't take me
但是你不能把我
You're also dragging me down.
也給拉下水啊
two days ago
前兩天
Just out of town
剛在外地
Made a big deal
做了一筆大買賣
Don't laugh, handsome guy
你別笑啊 帥哥
Are you in love?
談戀愛嗎你
The kind that pulls you into the water
拉你下水的那一種
Thank you everyone for coming
謝謝大家捧場
I'm done with my jokes
我的段子說完了
Thanks
谢谢
Another round of applause for this guy
再次掌聲送給這位
beautiful lady
美麗的小姐姐
alright
好了
Our talk show ends here today
今天我們脫口秀到這裡
It's over
就告一段落
There's another one next
接下來還有一位
The mysterious celebrity will appear
神秘大咖將會登場
Cool
酷啊
let's take a break
我們稍事休息
goodbye
再見
I think
我覺得啊
You are particularly suitable for talk shows
你特別適合去說脫口秀
look
你看
Obviously what he said is the truth
明明說的是真話
It sounds like a joke
聽著跟笑話似的
That’s all
都這樣了
You're not still thinking about him, are you?
你不會還想著他吧
what are you doing
你幹嘛呀
No one asked you to delete it
不是 誰讓你刪的
You have been made abnormal by him
你都被他弄得不正常了
Beauty
美女
can i buy you a drink
能請你喝一杯嗎
roll
滾
I go first
我先走了
Your luggage is still in my car
你行李還在我車裡呢
Pay the bill
買單
Sister Xi
熙姐
can i treat you to a meal
我能請你吃頓飯嗎
what
幹嘛
Thank you for your life-saving grace
感謝你的救命之恩啊
Let's talk to you by the way
順便和你聊聊
The moment I saw you in Macau
在澳門看見你那一刻
I really feel like I've been saved
我真覺著自己被救了
you are like a savior
你就像救世主一樣
I feel like you are behind this
我覺著你這背後啊
All with light
都帶著光
Didn't I tell you?
我不是跟你說過嗎
I will definitely protect your safety
我一定會保護你的安全
so
所以啊
I have to buy you a drink
我得請你喝一頓
next time
改天吧
you are now
你現在已經是
Gold player in the game
遊戲裡面的金牌玩家
When we meet in the future
以後咱們的見面
Be cautious
一定要謹慎
Those documents I took
我拿的那些文件
Have you dealt with everything?
都處理好了嗎
No big problem, right?
沒什麼大問題了吧
Don't worry, it's no problem
放心吧 沒問題
Then this matter
那這事
Does my dad know?
我爸知道嗎
after you leave
你走之後
We have all the files
文件我們都已經
Recovered
恢復好了
That's good, that's good
那就好 那就好
This is complicated enough
這事已經夠複雜的了
Don't let him know
千萬別讓他知道
Don't give it to him too
別把他也給
Hasn't he already seen it?
他不是已經見過
Yao Yao?
姚瑤了嗎
You probably know everything, right?
你該不會都知道了吧
what do you know
知道什麼
Yao Yao
姚瑤
is a spy
是間諜
Didn't I remind you?
我不是提醒過你嗎
She admitted it to you
她跟你承認了
Just because of this matter, I took action
就因為這件事動的手
That was an accident
那是偶然事件
Why did you come back alone?
你怎麼一個人回來了
Let's break up
分手了唄
Both of us
我們倆
It's impossible to be together
是不可能在一塊兒了
Why is she a spy?
她為什麼做間諜
Have you been trained?
受過訓練嗎
What have you done
幹過什麼
Who is online
上線是誰
Are there any other accomplices?
還有沒有其他同夥
Do you understand everything?
你都瞭解了嗎
You break up without knowing anything.
什麼都不知道你就分手
You are assisting
你這是在協助
do we work
我們工作嗎
Then I am
那我是
You shouldn't break up with her
不應該跟她分手啊
The moment of pain after the truth is revealed
真相揭穿後的一時痛苦
Human nature is understandable
人之常情 可以理解
But she has you under control
但她對你盡在掌握
You know nothing about her
你對她卻一無所知
Is this appropriate?
這合適嗎
inappropriate
不合適
But I can't go back
可我不能再回去
Find her
找她了吧
Don't you want to
你難道就不想
Know more about her?
瞭解她更多嗎
I know you still need it
我知道你還需要
a little time
一點時間
Go back and have a good rest first
先回去好好休息吧
Think about it carefully too
也仔細想一想
What I just told you
我剛才跟你說的話
I know
我知道
This journey is for you
這趟旅程對於你來說
Quite difficult
挺難的
Be vigilant
一定要保持警惕
They will come to you again
他們還會再來找你
You are no longer a
你也已經不再是個
An ordinary player
普通的玩家了
do you know
知道嗎
Get off the car
下車吧
I haven't arrived yet
我還沒到呢
I know
我知道啊
Stay alert
保持警惕嘛
Are you getting ready to close?
準備打烊了吧
you are the last guest
你是最後一位客人
what do you want to eat
想吃點什麼
But there aren’t many options left.
不過可選的不多了
Then you can eat whatever you want
那就有什麼吃什麼吧
If you don't dislike it
如果不嫌棄的話
Come have a work lunch with me
跟我一塊兒吃個工作餐
Can
可以
sit
坐
your work meal
你的工作餐
It’s too luxurious, right?
也太奢侈了吧
All done
都做了
Can't sell it tomorrow
明天也不能賣
Can only eat by myself
只能自己吃
Is that right?
那是不是
I have to pay a share
我要付一份錢啊
I can’t eat for free either.
我也不能白吃啊
I don't think you're eating for free.
我看你也不像是白吃的
Then I guess you
那我猜你
Will ask next
接下來會問
any drinks
喝點什麼
What to drink then?
那喝點什麼
sake bar
清酒吧
good
好
So do you have any good recommendations?
那你有什麼好的推薦嗎
Then I decided
那我決定了
Listen to you
聽你的
good
好
no problem
沒問題
Make an appointment to find a place
你約一個時間找個地方
I will look for you
我去找你
Something's wrong
有事啊
my brother
我弟弟
Just came back
這剛回來
Want to meet me
要約我見面
You have a brother
你還有弟弟
cousin
表弟
We grew up together since childhood
從小一起長大的
He's no different from his biological brother
跟親弟弟也沒什麼兩樣
Then your relationship must be very good
那你們感情一定很好
not good
不好
no tacit understanding
毫無默契
We haven’t been able to play together since we were little
從小就玩不到一塊兒去
But what happened later?
不過後來呢
Something happened to my family
我家就有了點變故
My father and mother are both gone
我爸我媽都不在了
I moved to my uncle's house
我就搬到了舅舅家
that period of time
那段時間
I just want to be in the room by myself
我只想自己在房間裡面
don't want to talk to anyone
不想跟任何人說話
The two of us started to get acquainted
我們倆就開始熟悉起來
The brother sleeping on the upper bunk
睡在上鋪的兄弟
I kept having nightmares during that time
我那段時間一直做噩夢
every time i wake up
我每次醒來
I saw him next to me
就看見他在旁邊
Whisper a spell to me
小聲地給我唸著咒語
spell
咒語
yes
是
I didn't know until later
後來我才知道
That's Harry Potter's spell
那個是哈利波特的咒語
Summon the patron saint
召喚守護神
Resist those who try to take you
抵制那些試圖把你
A nightmare pulled into the abyss
拉進深淵的夢魘
childish
幼稚
but it works
但很管用
yes
是啊
Slowly
慢慢呢
I'm willing to communicate with people
我就願意跟人交流了
he's like
他就像
Breaking my comfort zone
打破我舒適區的
alien visitor
異星來客
Suddenly broke into me and gave myself
突然闖進我給自己
In that restricted world
限制的那個天地裡面
Pull me out forcefully
硬生生地把我拉出來
perhaps
或許
It’s been a long time
是時間長了
Some pains gradually fade away
有些傷痛就慢慢淡了
Or maybe
又或許
He's such a chirper
他這個唧唧喳喳的
It's so noisy
吵死人了
I have to speak
我必須要開口
to shut him up
才能讓他閉嘴
so cute
很可愛
He's not cute
他 不可愛
I say you
我說你
I
我
I rarely see you talk so much
很少看你說這麼多話
Have the opportunity
有機會
Can you bring him here with you?
可以帶他一起來這兒啊
He's been in some trouble lately
他最近遇到了點麻煩
What trouble
什麼麻煩
All kinds of weird troubles
各種奇怪的麻煩
Young people
年輕人嘛
All like this
都這樣
You will always find your own direction
總會找到自己方向的
yes
是
It will be convenient for me in a while
一會兒我方便
Do you want to pack a chicken rice?
打包一個雞肉飯嗎
girlfriend
女朋友
It’s not appropriate to pack chicken rice, right?
打包雞肉飯不太合適吧
Then I'll make sushi
那要不然我做個壽司
Just chicken rice for colleagues
同事 雞肉飯就行
Sure
確定